Guide to the Robert College records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series II: Heritage Room/Rare Books (Istanbul & R.C./N.Y. Offices)
  - Trustees' memoranda, correspondence, memos from Murdoch (1979) (Box 8)
  - Wadsworth, Christopher (1994-1995) (Box 9)
  - C. Wadsworth (Box 9)
  - Christopher Wadsworth (1998) (Box 9)
  - Christopher Wadsworth (1999) (Box 9)
  - Christopher Wadsworth (2000) (Box 9)
  - Christopher Wadsworth Resignation (2000) (Box 9)
  - Christopher Wadsworth (2001) (Box 9)
  - Johnson, Margaret (Box 9)
  - Harry Dawe (1986-1991) (Box 9)
  - Chalfont: Correspondence to and from (1975) (2 Folders) (Box 9)
  - Chalfont: Correspondence to and from (1976) (2 Folders) (Box 9)
  - James Maggart: application and selection as Headmaster (1977) (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, reports to and from James Maggart (1977) (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, reports to and from James Maggart (1978) (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, reports to and from James Maggart (1979) (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, reports to and from James Maggart (1980) (Box 9)
  - A. Donn Kesselheim: Candidacy for position of Headmaster (1981) (Box 9)
  - A. Donn Kesselheim: Memos, correspondence with M. Murdoch (1982) (Box 9)
  - A. Donn Kesselheim: Correspondence and resignation (1983-1984) (Box 9)
  - The Robert College Story by Herbert H. Lane (Vol. II) (Box 25)
  - The Robert College Story by Herbert H. Lane (Vol. III) (Box 25)
  - Mary Miles Patrick and the American College for Girls at Istanbul in Turkey (Box 25)
  - Biography of Floyd Black RC-DCG (Box 27)
  - Interesting Unarchived Historical Documents:
    - Historical Info (Box 27)
    - Unarchived Historical Pieces (Box 27)
    - Historical Correspondence to Moore, H.S. Coffin, P. Monroe,Caleb Gates (Box 27)
    - Ray, Garo Willard '22 A CI (Box 27)
    - Analysis & Study of Library Media Center '89 (Box 27)
  - The Orient (incomplete files) (1919) (Box 27)
  - The Orient (incomplete files) (1920) (Box 27)
  - The Orient (plus duplicates for 1920-incomplete files) (1921) (Box 28)
  - Robert College Debate Union Chronicles (April/May 1930) (Box 28)
  - Turkish Translation Service (1931-1937) (Box 28)
  - The Orient (plus one issue January 1923) (1922) (Box 28)
  - The Orient (1912-1913) (Box 29)
  - The Orient (incomplete file) (1910-1911) (Box 29)
  - L'Opinion (1981-1983) (Box 29)
  - Bingham Autobiography, Vol. I (1988-1989) (Box 29)
  - Bingham Autobiography, Vol. II & III (1989-1990 1990-1991) (Box 29)
  - The Bosphorus Chronicle (ca. 1971-1985) (Box 29)
  - Cagri (1983-1985) (Box 29)
  - Cagri (ca. 1985-1995) (Box 30)
  - Objective (1986) (Box 30)
  - Publications (Objective, Kaleidoscope) (1987) (Box 30)
  - The Bosphorus Chronicle, 1986-1987 (Box 31)
  - The Bosphorus Chronicle; October 1994 #1, November 10 1994 #2, November 1994 #3 (Box 31)
  - Istanbul American Colleges, Alumni Bulletin (1952 1953, 1954, 1957, 1960-1961, 1955 1966) (Box 31)
  - Istanbul American Colleges, Alumni Bulletin (1966-1968) (Box 31)
  - Robert College Alumni Magazine (1972-1975) (Box 31)
  - Robert College Alumni Magazine (1977-1978) (Box 31)
  - Robert College-Winter 1987/1988 (Box 32)
  - Muhasebesi (Box 32)
  - Istanbul American Colleges, Alumni Bulletin 1962, 1964-1965 (Box 32)
  - Robert College Quarterly 1992-2001 (Box 32)
  - Robert College Quarterly 2002-2006 (Box 32)
  - Reports of US Annual Giving (Box 32)
  - Robert College Newsletters (1990-1997) (Box 32)
  - Adams, Kathyrn N (Box 33)
  - Akkoyunlu, Bedia (Box 33)
  - Alpar, Nahit (Box 33)
  - Antel, Nazime (Box 33)
  - Armstrong, George S. (Box 33)
  - Baker, Stephen (Box 33)
  - Ballantine, Duncan (Box 33)
  - Barker, James (Box 33)
  - Bayindir, Gokce (Box 33)
  - Beard, Anson M. (1948-1957 ?) (Box 33)
  - Begdes, Kutsi (Box 33)
  - Bingham, William H. (-1937) (Box 33)
  - Bliss, Collins P. (Box 33)
  - Boschen, Henry C. (-1966) (Box 33)
  - Brown, Philip M. (-1932) (Box 33)
  - Brown, Moreau D. (1947-1956) (Box 33)
  - Brown, Moreau D. (1957-1963) (Box 33)
  - Brown, Moreau D. (1964-1976) (Box 33)
  - Brown, William A. (1926-1930) (Box 34)
  - Brown, William A. (1931-1932) (Box 34)
  - Brown, William A. (1933-1943) (Box 34)
  - Brownell, Katherine D. (1949-1963) (Box 34)
  - Brownell, Katherine D. (1964-1983) (Box 34)
  - Burgess, W. Randolph (1927-1967) (Box 34)
  - Cakmak, Ahmet (1975-1983) (Box 34)
  - Calder, Frederick C. (Box 34)
  - Carey, Jane C. (1955-1981) (Box 34)
  - Cary, William L. (-1974) (Box 34)
  - Case, Anne T. (1950-) (Box 34)
  - Cavusoglu, Ahmet (1977-) (Box 34)
  - Childs, Timothy W. (Correspondence) (Box 34)
  - Books-Joy of Service (RC) (E. Clarke) (Box 35)
  - Clarke, Elizabeth Dodge Huntington (1-7 of 9 Folders) (Box 35)
  - Clarke, Elizabeth Dodge Huntington (8-9 of 9 Folders) (Box 36)
  - Cochran, Homer P. (1944-1947) (Box 36)
  - Coons, Richard (-1981) (Box 36)
  - DeForest, Robert W. (-1930) (Box 36)
  - Devres, Mehmet (Box 36)
  - Diker, Vecdi (1959-1962 1967-1972) (Box 36)
  - Dinger, Elliot A. (Box 36)
  - Dodge, Cleveland (Box 36)
  - Dodge, David S. (-1962) (Box 36)
  - Dodge, Grace Hoadley (1908-1914) (Box 36)
  - Dorr, Goldwaithe H. (1948-1959) (Box 36)
  - Dorr, Goldwaithe H. (1960-1969) (Box 36)
  - Dorr, Goldwaithe H. (1970-1978) (Box 36)
  - Dorr, Russell H. (1962-1980) (Box 36)
  - Duggan, Stephen P. (-1947) (Box 36)
  - Durust, Hamdi (Box 36)
  - Dutton, Samuel (-1919) (Box 36)
  - Eczacibasi, Nejat (1966-1971) (Box 36)
  - Eren, Hon. Nuri (Correspondence) (Box 36)
  - Erul, Omer (Box 36)
  - Esty, John C., Jr. (1974-1989) (Box 36)
  - Everton, John Scott (Box 36)
  - Robert College- Vol. 2 No. 1 (February 1983); Vol. 3 No. 3 (Fall 1984); Vol. 4 No. 1 (Box 37)
  - (Fall 1985); Vol. 5 No. 1 (Spring 1986) (Box 37)
  - Faust, Walter L. (1949-1951) (Box 37)
  - Few, Benjamin (1945-1958) (Box 37)
  - Forbes, Rose d. (Mrs. Malcolm J.) (Box 37)
  - Foster, Austin T. (1958-1960) (Box 37)
  - Franklin, George S. (1949-1977) (Box 37)
  - Friendly, Alfred (1983-) (Box 37)
  - Friendly, Jean (Box 37)
  - Furgac, Melike (Box 37)
  - Goheen, Robert (1956) (Box 37)
  - Goodsell, Fred F. (Box 37)
  - Grosvenor, Melville B. (Box 37)
  - Garland, Charles S. (-1947) (Box 37)
  - Guest, John S. (1978-1990) (Box 37)
  - Gordon, Mary R. (Box 37)
  - Haines, T. Davies (-1968) (Box 37)
  - Hanks, Nancy (1963-1969) (Box 37)
  - Harrington, John L. (1927-1941) (Box 37)
  - Hatch, Harold (-1946) (Box 37)
  - Hazen, David C. (Box 37)
  - Hazen, Harold (1954-1980) (5 Folders) (Box 38)
  - Henninger, Kenneth A. (1975-1982) (Box 38)
  - Hibbs, Sherlock (Box 38)
  - Hibbs, Sherlock (II) (Box 38)
  - Hill, Raymond Dunlap (Box 38)
  - Hilton, Henry (1931-) (Box 38)
  - Holt, Henry C. (1925-1949) (3 Folders) (Box 39)
  - Huntington, George H. (Box 39)
  - Huntington, Thomas (1953-1985) (Box 39)
  - Inal, Kenan (1957) (Box 39)
  - Ipecki, Abdi (1968-1976) (Box 39)
  - Isvan, Amet (1963-) (Box 39)
  - Karacabey, Ayla (1974-) (Box 39)
  - Karahan, Oguz (1973-1977) (Box 39)
  - Kardem, Frank (1959-) (Box 39)
  - Keil, Francis C. (Box 39)
  - Kemmerer, Edwin W. (Box 39)
  - Kerwin, Robert W. (1971-1982) (Box 39)
  - Keyes, Harold B. (Box 39)
  - Kurdas, Kemal (Box 39)
  - Kuyucak, Hazim Atif (Box 39)
  - Lanckton, Arthur L. (1954-1968) (Box 39)
  - Lipscomb, Thomas (1974-) (Box 39)
  - Katipoglu, Sadun (1961-1974) (Box 39)
  - Kimball, Grace N. (Box 39)
  - Kirac, Suna (Box 39)
  - Kozlu, Cem M. (1997-) (Box 39)
  - Koptagel, Gunsel (1969-) (Box 39)
  - Kuran, Aptullah (1974-1994) (Box 39)
  - Lawrence, Barbara C. (1989-1996) (Box 39)
  - Lawrence, James (1969-1983) (3 Folders) (Box 39)
  - MacAdams, Howard B. (-1973) (Box 39)
  - Mardin, Yusuf (1977-) (Box 39)
  - McMenamin, Joan (Box 39)
  - Morris, Grinnell (1946-1974) (Box 39)
  - Neyzi, Ali (Box 39)
  - Nichols, Howard B. (Box 40)
  - Niemeyer, John H. (1958-1972) (Box 40)
  - Norton, Garrison (1960-1968) (Box 40)
  - Ogden, Alfred (Box 40)
  - Page, Jane N.-Correspondence (1959-1980) (Box 40)
  - Page, Jane N.-Correspondence (1981-1998) (Box 40)
  - Page, Jane N. (GIFTS) (Box 40)
  - Perkins, Linn M. (Box 40)
  - Radomisli, Aylin (1983-1986) (Box 40)
  - Ratte, John (Box 40)
  - Rice, Charles (1975-1979) (Box 40)
  - Sabar, Ergun (Box 40)
  - Schieffelin, Bayard (-1985) (Box 40)
  - Estate of Bayard Shieffelin (Box 40)
  - Sofia American Schools 1963-1977 (Box 40)
  - Sofia American Schools (1978-1979) (Box 40)
  - Sofia American Schools (1979-1980) (Box 40)
  - Sofia American Schools (1980-1981) (Box 40)
  - Sofia American Schools (1981-1982) (Box 40)
  - Sofia American Schools (1982-1983) (Box 40)
  - Sofia American Schools (1983-1984) (Box 40)
  - Sofia American Schools (1984-1985) (Box 40)
  - Sofia American Schools (1985-1986) (Box 40)
  - Sofia American Schools(1986-1987) (Box 41)
  - Sofia American Schools (1987-1988) (Box 41)
  - Sofia American Schools (1988-1989) (Box 41)
  - Sofia American Schools (1989-1990) (Box 41)
  - Sofia American Schools (1990-1991) (Box 41)
  - Sofia American Schools (1991-1992) (Box 41)
  - Sofia American Schools (1992-1993) (Box 41)
  - Terzioglu, Meliha (1963-) (Box 41)
  - Tweedy, Mary J.-Correspondence (1963-1995) (Box 41)
  - Tumer, Irfan (1973-1995) (Box 41)
  - Ulusoy, Melahat (1975-1979) (Box 41)
  - Umur, Aydin (1971-1975) (Box 41)
  - Ustundag, Ustun (1971-1975) (Box 41)
  - Yalcin, Nilufer (1974-1993) (Box 41)
  - Yazici, Bulent (1961-1972) (Box 41)
  - Yuregir, Gunes (-1982) (Box 41)
  - Zinsser, Barbara L.-Correspondence (1955-1997) (Box 41)
  - Zobu, Perihan (1971-1975) (Box 41)
  - Patent (Tanyolac Odor Measurement Device) File (1964) (2 Folders) (Box 42)
  - Patent File: Final Technical Report on Development of Odor (Box 42)
  - Measuring Instrument (1965) (Box 42)
  - Patent File: Reports (1964-1966) (Box 42)
  - Patent File (1965-1966) (Box 42)
  - Patent File (1966-1967) (Box 42)
  - Patent File: Tanyolac's Correspondence (1964-1972) (Box 42)
  - Patent File: Tanyolac Correspondence re: Tanyolac Patents (1965-1969) (Box 42)
  - Patent File: Patents and Research (1967-1968) (Box 43)
  - Patent File: Patents and Research (1968-1969) (Box 43)
  - Patent File: NATO Conference on Odor Management (1965-1966) (Box 43)
  - Research Center: Surveys and Annual Reports (1966-1969) (Box 43)
  - Correspondence re: Research Center (1961-1968) (not inclusive) (Box 43)
  - Headmaster's Report: Margaret Johnson (Acting Head) (1985) (Box 43)
  - Headmaster's Report: Harry A. Dawe (November 1986) (Box 43)
  - Headmaster's Report: Harry A. Dawe (November 1987) (Box 43)
  - Headmaster's Report: (10 November 1988) (Box 43)
  - Harry A. Dawe (February, May, November 1988) (Box 43)
  - Headmaster's Report: Harry A. Dawe (November 1989) (Box 43)
  - Headmaster's Report: Harry A. Dawe (May, November 1990) (Box 43)
  - Headmaster's Report: Cornelius Bull (covers 1960-1966) (1967) (Box 43)
  - Headmaster's Report: J. Chalfant (1971-1972) (Box 43)
  - Headmaster's Report: J. Chalfant (1972-1973) (Box 43)
  - Headmaster's Report: J. Chalfant (1974-1975) (Box 43)
  - Headmaster's Report: J. Chalfant (1975-1976) (Box 43)
  - Headmaster's Report: J. Chalfant (1976-1977) (Box 43)
  - Headmaster's Report: Jim Maggart (1977-1978) (Box 44)
  - Annual Report of the Headmaster: Jim Maggart (1979-1980) (Box 44)
  - Summary of Meeting with Trustees: Jim Maggart (1979) (Box 44)
  - Annual Report of the Headmaster: Jim Maggart (20 June 1981) (Box 44)
  - Annual Report of the Headmaster: A. Donn Kesselheim (1981-1982) (Box 44)
  - Annual Report of the President: A. Donn Kesselheim (1982-1983) (Box 44)
  - Headmaster's Report: Progress Report-A. Donn Kesselheim (1983-1984) (Box 44)
  - Headmaster's Report: (January 1984) (Box 44)
  - Headmistress' Report to Board of Trustees: Margaret Johnson (November 1984) (Box 44)
  - Materials Relating to the Reorganization of RC (August 1970) (Box 44)
  - Materials Relating to the Reorganization of RC (Sept-Oct 1970) (Box 44)
  - Materials Relating to the Reorganization of RC (Nov-Dec 1970) (Box 44)
  - Materials Relating to the Reorganization of RC (Jan 1971) (Box 44)
  - Materials Relating to the Reorganization of RC (Feb 1971) (Box 44)
  - Materials Relating to the Reorganization of RC (March-April 1971) (Box 44)
  - Reports of the Chairman to the Board of Trustees (1971-1972) (Box 44)
  - Materials Relating to the Reorganization of RC (March-April 1971) (Box 45)
  - Materials Relating to the Reorganization of RC (April-May 1971) (Box 45)
  - Materials Relating to the Reorganization of RC (May-June 1971) (Box 45)
  - Materials Relating to the Reorganization of RC (June-March 1972) (Box 45)
  - Correspondence & legal Documents re: founding of Bogazicic University (June-September 1971) (Box 45)
  - Establishment of Bosphorus University (Aug 1971-Sept 1971) (Box 45)
  - Establishment of Bosphorus University (Sept 1971) (Box 45)
  - Establishment of Bosphorus University (Oct 1971-June 1972) (Box 45)
  - Establishment of Bosphorus University (incl. Development Plan, 1971-1972) (June 1971-Nov 1972 1976) (Box 45)
  - Reports from the Chairman to Board of Trustees (1970-1971) (Box 45)
  - Ad Hoc Committee: Looking into costs of the Merged Lycee (1971) (Box 45)
  - Ad Hoc Committee: Looking into costs of the Merged Lycee: (1972) (Box 45)
  - Establishment of Bosphorus University (July 1971) (Box 46)
  - Summary Contribution Reports and Memos (1969-1972) (Box 46)
  - Establishment of Bosphorus University (incl. proposed "Law of Bosphorus University" (Jan-July 1971) (Box 46)
  - Memoranda to Board of Trustees (Lawrence, page) re: Reorganization of RC (1971) (Box 46)
  - "Correspondence with the Field" to/from Everton, Chalfont, Page (1971) (Box 46)
  - "Correspondence with the Field" with Everton, Chalfont, Aptullah Kuran (1971) (Box 46)
  - "Correspondence with the Field" incl. correspondence with Everton (1971) (Box 46)
  - "Correspondence with the Field" with Everton, Aptullah Kuran, Chalfont (1971-1972) (Box 46)
  - "Correspondence with the Field" with Chalfont, Page (Box 46)
  - "Correspondence with the Field" to/from Everton, Page (1971) (Box 46)
  - Lawrence-Everton Correspondence (1969-1970) (1 of 3 Folders) (Box 46)
  - Lawrence-Everton Correspondence (1969-1970) (2-3 of 3 Folders) (Box 47)
  - Development Committee: Memos, Reports, Correspondence (1966-1970) (Box 47)
  - Development Committee: Correspondence, Memos, Reports (1970) (2 Folders) (Box 47)
  - Development Committee: Memoranda, reports, Correspondence, (1971) (2 Folders) (Box 47)
  - Trustee Development Committee Material: Correspondence, Memoranda (1977 1981) (Box 47)
  - Development committee materials (1982-1972 not inclusive) (Box 48)
  - Resolutions on Trustee deaths (1976 1979) (Box 48)
  - Lawrence's Situation Reports (1971) (Box 48)
  - Lawrence's Situation Reports (1970-1971) (Box 48)
  - Jane Page's Situation Reports (1970-1975) (Box 48)
  - Trustee's Agenda and Minutes (1972) (Box 48)
  - Ad Hoc Cost Committee Reports (1972) (Box 48)
  - Trustees' Agenda and Minutes (1971) (Box 48)
  - Memos, reports and correspondence from N.Y. Office (1973) (Box 48)
  - Memoranda by laws re: Reorganization of R.C. (1968-1970) (Box 48)
  - "Committee of Three"-Ad Hoc Implementation committee re: (Box 48)
  - Reorganization of RC-memos, correspondence (1971) (Box 48)
  - Annual Report for A.I.D. (1973-1974) (Box 48)
  - J.C.C.F.-Selection of Director (Box 48)
  - Selection of Director for Jane Coffins Child Memorial Fund for Medical Research (1975) (Box 48)
  - RC Alumni Contributors to the 125th Year Book and Art Exhibit (May 13-May 27, 1989) (Box 49)
  - Heritage Room (Box 49)
  - Planning Committee Papers (March-Sept 1969) (Box 49)
  - Notes on Planning Comm. Meetings-Washington, NY & Istanbul & Exhibits I of II (Box 49)
  - Notes on Planning Comm. Meetings-Washington, NY & Istanbul & Exhibits II of II (Box 49)
  - Summary of principal topics for Trustees planning comm. & Memos (1969) (Box 49)
  - Marjory Hyde Bond Book-Minutes & Interviews in the USA (Box 49)
  - Norton Report: Planning Committee-May 1967 (Box 49)
  - Planning Committee (1966-1967) (2 Folders) (Box 49)
  - Planning Committee-Dorr Memo (1967) (Box 50)
  - Planning Committee-Statement by Alfred Ogden (October 1969) (Box 50)
  - Planning Committee (April-June 1967) (Box 50)
  - Turkish Ministry of Education-Educational Reform (1971) I of II (Box 50)
  - Witt Report-Audiovisual Instruction (Box 50)
  - Petersen Task Force Report (1970-1971) (Box 50)
  - Peat, Marwick Mitchell & Co (1971) (Box 50)
  - Nystrom Report (Box 50)
  - Northrop Report-Secondary Math Study (Box 50)
  - Newsom Report (Box 50)
  - MacPhail Report- April 28, 1969 (Box 50)
  - Hennessey Report (Box 50)
  - Finch Report (Box 50)
  - Foshay, Dr. Arthur W., 1972-Consultant (Box 50)
  - Sherrill Cleland Report (May 1970) (Box 50)
  - Bartlett Report (June 1970) (Box 50)
  - Planning Committee: Sparks Report-March 1969 (Box 50)
  - Planning Committee: Space Studies (Box 50)
  - Ford Foundation Files: (Box 51)
    - English Language-Teaching Equipment-Grant #1 (28 Feb, 1962) (Box 51)
    - English Language-Teaching Materials-Reports on Grant #2 (Box 51)
    - English Language-Teaching Textbooks-Grant #3, 4/28/1966 (Box 51)
    - Reports on Grant #3 (Box 51)
    - English Language-Teaching Textbook-Grant #4 62-174C, 5/27/1968 (Box 51)
    - Operating Expense Grant (Box 51)
    - Teacher Recruitment Program (Dean Travel Grant) (Box 51)
    - English Language Teaching Textbooks and additional equipment Reports On Grant #4 (Box 51)
    - Grants #690-0654-Financing Planning Consultants (Box 51)
    - Grants#700-0020-Research and Undergraduate Teaching in Economics (Box 51)
    - (Proposal, Grant and Correspondence) (Box 51)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Files:
    - General (Box 51)
    - Vote on Release of 5% of Rockefeller Funds, 1969 (Box 51)
    - Correspondence (Box 51)
    - Turkish Faculty Training Fellowships #RF56187 (Reports) (Box 51)
    - Turkish Faculty Training Fellowships #RF56187 (Letters) (Box 51)
    - Humanities Project Grant #58065 (Box 51)
    - Humanities Project Grant #58065 (Reports) (Box 51)
    - Proposal-Columbia University/RC Business School-Rockefeller Brothers Fund (Box 51)
    - Turkish Faculty Training Fellowships #RF56187 (Box 51)
    - Business Management Proposal (Box 51)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund-RC School of Bus. Adm. & Economics (Box 51)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund-RC Schools of Bus. Adm. & Economics Proposal (Box 52)
    - Annual and Quarterly Reports, etc.-Rockefeller Foundation (Box 52)
  - Grace H. Dodge Fund (Box 52)
  - Dodge Foundation Gift (Box 52)
  - Mrs. Sarah Dodge Gift (Box 52)
  - Dodge Family Gift (Box 52)
  - Anne T. Case Memorial Fund (Box 52)
  - John C. Case-Turkish Travel Fellow (Box 52)
  - Chase Manhattan International Foundation (Box 52)
  - Estate of Cornelis Beets (Box 52)
  - Estate of Amy Briggs Baldwin (Box 52)
  - The Grant Foundation-Reports R. Academy Comm. Rep. Program (Box 52)
  - Grant Foundation-Play center and Child study project (Proposal and correspondence) (Box 52)
  - American Machine and Foundry Co. AMF Foundation (Box 52)
  - Press Releases-Formation of Bogazici (Box 52)
  - Annual Giving Gift Analysis Report (Box 52)
  - Warner Pomerene (Box 52)
  - Lee Fonger Library Fund #122-9033 (1971) (Box 52)
  - Turkish Educational Foundation (Box 53)
  - AKC Fund (Box 53)
  - Estate of James Lawrence (Box 53)
  - Palmer, Caroline Damon (Trust For) (Box 53)
  - Lilly, Endowment Inc. (Box 53)
  - Weller Foundation (Box 53)
  - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation (Box 53)
  - Estate of Frank P. Sheppard (Box 53)
  - Estate of Sarah Stone Miller (Box 53)
  - The Singer Company Foundation (Box 53)
  - The Rubicon Foundation (Box 53)
  - Estate of Eleanor S. Upton (Box 53)
  - Etna Martin Craft Trust (from Elizabeth Dodge Huntington) (Box 53)
  - Vella & Dudley Templeton Memorial Fund (Box 53)
  - Mrs. Thomas J. Watson Foundation (Box 53)
  - Estate of Henry A. Wolsdorf (Box 53)
  - Caleb C. and Julian W. Dula Educational and Charitable Foundation (Box 53)
  - Thomas H. Huntington Trust (Box 53)
  - Papazian (Andon) (Box 53)
  - Estate of Elbis Papazian (1965-1968) (Box 53)
  - Correspondence: Arthur B./John W. Emmons Trust Funds (1956-1957) (Box 53)
  - Correspondence: Emmons Trust Funds (1957-1961) (Box 53)
  - Correspondence: Emmons Trust Funds (1961-1965) (Box 53)
  - Estate of Alphild Yesim (Box 53)
  - Records Relating to the Estate of Alphid Yesim (1975-1978) (Box 53)
  - Estate of Katherine Brownell (Box 53)
  - Estate of Sprio K. Kostof (Box 53)
  - Foundations-General Correspondence (Box 53)
  - Contributions to the Building Fund (1985-1989) (Box 53)
  - RC/Henninger Financial Reports (1975-1982) (Box 54)
  - RC/Henninger Application for AID Grants (1979-1981) (Box 54)
  - RC/Ogden Transfer Documents: Power of Attorney (1971) (Box 54)
  - RC/Ogden Supporting Documents: Land Transfer (1971) (Box 54)
  - RC/Ogden Correspondence: Reorganization of RC; Land Transfer (1971-1973) (Box 54)
  - RC/Ogden Correspondence (1973-1974) (Box 54)
  - RC/Ogden Land Development and Taxes (1973-1974) (Box 54)
  - RC/Ogden Title Deeds (1972) (Box 54)
  - RC/Ogden Memoranda re: Transfer or Property (1971 1974-1975) (Box 54)
  - RC/Ogden Sale of Excess Lands: Memoranda, Legal Documents (1970-1974) (Box 54)
  - RC/Ogden "The Triangle" Land Transfer - Legal Documents, Memoranda, Correspondence (1973-1979) (Box 54)
  - RC/Ogden Legal Opinions: Correspondence, Memos, Excerpts (1965-1970) (Box 54)
  - RC/Ogden Records re: Settlement with Mary Ward Kerby (Box 54)
  - RC/Ogden Records Relating to AIRCO Retirement Fund for Faculty (1967-1974) (Box 55)
  - RC/Ogden Records Relation to AIRCO Retirement Fund for Faculty (1974-1976) (Box 55)
  - RC/Ogden Supporting Documents re: Bosphorus University, Protocol or Memorandum of Understanding (1970-1971) (Box 55)
  - RC/Ogden Court Order: Bebek Campus (1971) (Box 55)
  - RC/Ogden Board of Regents: Correspondence (1971) (Box 55)
  - RC/Ogden Constitutional Court Filing re: Civil Engineers Diplomas (1971) (Box 55)
  - A.I.D. Grant Correspondence and Document (1971) (Box 55)
  - RC/Ogden Hisar Foundation Official Documents (1970) (Box 55)
  - RC/Ogden Correspondence, Memoranda re: Merger with ACG (1957-1958) (Box 55)
  - RC/Ogden Correspondence, Memoranda re: Merger with ACG (1958) (Box 55)
  - RC/Ogden Certification of Incorporation (1959) (Box 55)
  - RC/Ogden Reorganization of RC: Protocol of Understanding (1971) (Box 55)
  - RC/Ogden General Correspondence and Memoranda (1972-1976) (Box 56)
  - RC/Ogden General Correspondence and Memoranda (1976-1979) (Box 56)
  - RC/Ogden General Correspondence and Memoranda (1979-1985) (Box 56)
  - RC/Ogden Correspondence, Memos: 100th Anniversary (1963) (Box 56)
  - RC/Ogden Correspondence, Memos: 100th Anniversary (1962) (Box 56)
  - RC/Ogden Correspondence, Memos: 100th Anniversary (1962) (Box 56)
  - RC/Ogden Correspondence, Memos: 100th Anniversary (1962) (Box 56)
  - RC/Ogden Correspondence, Memos: 100th Anniversary (1961-1962) (Box 56)
  - RC/Ogden Memos, Correspondence re: "Future of the College" (1970) (Box 56)
  - RC/Ogden Correspondence, Memos re: "Future of the College" (1970-1971) (Box 56)
  - RC/Henninger Termination and Retirement Fund (1979-1980) (Box 57)
  - RC/Henninger Unexpected Plant Funds (1979-1981) (Box 57)
  - RC/Henninger RC Endowment Funds; Aetna Warbury Investment Management (1982) (Box 57)
  - RC/Henninger Fiscal Year Reports (1976-1978) (Box 57)
  - RC/Henninger Fiscal Year Reports (1979) (Box 57)
  - RC/Henninger Hisar Foundation (1974-1976) (Box 57)
  - RC/Henninger Pensions, Benefits, Contracts (1975-1982) (Box 57)
  - RC/Henninger Fiscal Year Reports (1980) (Box 57)
  - RC/Henninger Fiscal Year Reports (1981-1982) (Box 57)
  - RC/Henninger RC Expatriate Taxation (1977) (Box 57)
  - RC/Henninger RC Expatriate Taxation (1977-1981) (Box 57)
  - RC/Henninger Budget (1976-1980) (Box 57)